# Pavitra Pati

### Professional Summary

If given a chance I will work undoubtedly and with utter sincerity towards my role in the organization. I have worked on stage for a long time now i but love to work at the backend aka on Coding and Game development. I truly am looking forward to work with EXPERTS aka MEMBERS OF ORGANISATION and to learn from them and grow even more.

## Employment history

#### Extra course, Python.

Jan. 2021 - Present

 Currently ongoing python courses on CISCO, SOLOLEARN, and COURSERA.

# 3D modelling, Animation and Game development, Blender and Unity.

Jan. 2020 - Mar. 2020

- Have been interested in 3D modelling and game development for a long time.
- Have worked with BLENDER regarding 3D modelling and some basic animation.
- · Have very minimal Game development skill.
- · Still working on Blender and Unity to improve my skills.

#### Organiser, Advocate and delegate, Model United Nation. Surat, Gujarat

Jan. 2018 - Jan. 2020

- Successfully organized a MUN event comprising 200 people in the year 2020.
- Have participated in 3 MUN and won the BEST DELEGATE award twice (2018-19) and BEST ADVOCATE (2020).

# Protagonist of drama, poetic drama and Kavita fest, Surat drama club. Surat, Gujarat

Jan. 2017 - Dec. 2018

. I believe I have quite good oratory skill and am a quick learner

### Education

Delhi Public School Surat, Surat, Gujarat

AISSCE, PCM, Mar. 2020

Delhi Public School Tapi, Surat, Gujarat

AISSE, CBSE, Feb. 2018

#### Personal info

Phone:

6354506086

Email:

pavitrapati@karunya.edu.in

Address:

971B Indraprasth nagar, Kaliyabid, Bhavnagar, 364001 (IN)

#### Skills

Html



Unity



Blender



Python



C

